Kheel Center AV Collection 6118 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Debs, Eugene V. Eugene V. Debs - Trade Unionist, Socialist, Revolutionary, 1855-1926 - #110 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 451)
  - Debs, Eugene V. Eugene V. Debs - Trade Unionist, Socialist, Revolutionary, 1855-1926 - (Box 451)
    #110 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- [Unlabelled] - #136 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 452)
  - [Unlabelled] - (Box 452)
    #136 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees. District 1199. Take Care: A Musical Revue of Life in the Hospitals. - #137 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 453)
  - National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees. District 1199. Take Care: A Musical Revue of Life in the Hospitals. - (Box 453)
    #137 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Seeger, Pete. Archive of Folk Music: The House Carpenter., Paddy Works On the Railroad., Arivan the Greenland Fisheries., and others - #139 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 454)
  - Seeger, Pete. Archive of Folk Music: The House Carpenter., Paddy Works On the Railroad., Arivan the Greenland Fisheries., and others - (Box 454)
    #139 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees. District 1199. Ossie and Ruby, and Bread and Roses. - #138 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 455)
  - National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees. District 1199. Ossie and Ruby, and Bread and Roses. - (Box 455)
    #138 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Works Many Voices, Volume 1. Songs of work Re-issued. Down Home Music / Arhoolie Records. - #141 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 456)
  - Works Many Voices, Volume 1. Songs of work Re-issued. Down Home Music / Arhoolie Records. - (Box 456)
    #141 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Works Many Voices, Volume 2. Songs of work Re-issued. Down Home Music / Arhoolie Records. - #142 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 457)
  - Works Many Voices, Volume 2. Songs of work Re-issued. Down Home Music / Arhoolie Records. - (Box 457)
    #142 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Halker, Bucky. Stepn Blue. Revolting Records, 1986. - #145 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 458)
  - Halker, Bucky. Stepn Blue. Revolting Records, 1986. - (Box 458)
    #145 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Glazer. Joe. Singing BRAC for BRACs 75th Anniversary. - #147 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 459)
  - Glazer. Joe. Singing BRAC for BRACs 75th Anniversary. - (Box 459)
    #147 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- International Ladies Garment Workers Union. Two, Two for the Union. Two Presidents of the United States - Kennedy and Johnson and two Garment Workers...talk about the ILGWU - #148 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 460)
  - International Ladies Garment Workers Union. Two, Two for the Union. Two Presidents of the United States - Kennedy and Johnson and two Garment Workers...talk about the ILGWU - (Box 460)
    #148 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- International Ladies Garment Workers Union. The Northeast Sings. Presented by the Northeast Department at the 32nd Convention of the ILGWU, Miami Beach, FL, ca. 1964? - #149 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 461)
  - International Ladies Garment Workers Union. The Northeast Sings. Presented by the Northeast Department at the 32nd Convention of the ILGWU, Miami Beach, FL, ca. 1964? - (Box 461)
    #149 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Justice in America - For All My Union Friends. Billings, MT: Jester Sound Studio; with the Gairrett Brothers - Jess Wilcox. - #151 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 462)
  - Justice in America - For All My Union Friends. Billings, MT: Jester Sound Studio; with the Gairrett Brothers - Jess Wilcox. - (Box 462)
    #151 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Solidarity Day I - Commemorative - item #134 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 463)
  - Solidarity Day I - Commemorative - (Box 463)
    #134 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Solidarity Day III music - item #135 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 464)
  - Solidarity Day III music - (Box 464)
    #135 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- A Union's Story / The International Brotherhood of Teamsters (Box 465)
- see folder list for contents (Box 466)
  - National Interfaith Committee for Worker Justice / Faith & Work [belongs to collection #6414 AV], 1996; 27 (Box 466)
  - Future Shop: A Modular Manufacturing Shop, 26 (Box 466)
  - Through Strength and Struggle (English Audio): copyrighted 5/88, 1988; 25 (Box 466)
  - 1995 UNITE Convention Highlights, 24 (Box 466)
  - Convention of Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees, AFL-CIO, CLC - Miami Beach, Florida: June 29-30, 1995, 23 (Box 466)
  - Never Surrender, Local 26 [collection #/3012 AV: ff22, 22 (Box 466)
  - Frances Fox Piven: Nov. 30, 1995 [collection #/3012 AV], 21 (Box 466)
  - Good Jobs! / Waterbury CT 2000, Local Hiring Campaign [belongs to collection #6414 AV], 28 (Box 466)
  - Leon Davis, Spr. '76, George Brooks' Class (Collection /4038 AV), 1976; 1 (Box 466)
    housed here
  - Leon Davis, Spr. '76, George Brooks' Class (Collection /4038 AV), 1976; 2 (Box 466)
  - Maurice Neufeld - I and LR - The Future of the American Labor Movement, 4/10/1953 - (Collection /4229 AV), 3 (Box 466)
  - Konvitz Service, 10/26/2003 (Collection /4242 AV), 4 (Box 466)
  - WTC Forum - 9/21/2001 (belongs to collection # /4289 AV), 5 (Box 466)
    being housed here
  - Chicago Radical Jewish Elders, Marvin Rogoff Union Leader Interview, August 18, 2006 by Marvin Lehrman (collection 6236 AV), 6 (Box 466)
  - Toukatly, Luanna - Alexsis Risk Management File - 4/13/1991 - T. Kelley, 7 (Box 466)
    collection 6275 AV
  - Moved back to 6275 AV, 8 (Box 466)
  - Moved back to 6275 AV, 9 (Box 466)
  - NLRB Photos, Bf/o, 4/27/01, 2001; 10 (Box 466)
  - Harvesting Hometown Jobs: a small town guide to local economic development / National Association of Towns and Townships, 11 (Box 466)
  - Original Films of Frank B. Gilbreth; The Quest for the One Best Way: Belongs to 6027 AV, 12 (Box 466)
  - Interview - Miller-Farcey-Korman: edited Feb. 1, 1973 // Collection /4311, 13 (Box 466)
    belongs to collection /4311, found in box 1, being housed here
  - [e] access: Leadership Development Series, 14 (Box 466)
    transferred from Catherwood Library collection - 2/2015
  - Schmatta: Rags to riches to Rags - 10/19/2009, 15 (Box 466)
    #463 -- 1 vhs - removed from box 11, ff6 and put here
  - Bill Whyte Panel Presentation - 6/5/1994: Collection # /4149 AV, 16 (Box 466)
  - No Barriers for Business Implementing the Americans with Disabilities Act, 17 (Box 466)
    Accompanying text is in ff 18
  - No Barriers for Business Implementing the Americans with Disabilities Act (text to accompany VHS tape in ff 17), 18 (Box 466)
  - Practical Dreamer: The Leon Davis Story, 19 (Box 466)
  - Proud to be Union / ACTWU, 20 (Box 466)
- Tejid@s Junt@s: Workers, Students, and the Movement for Alta Gracia (Box 467)
- The Inheritance (Box 468)
- Textiles: NBCTV a.m. (Today) -- 11/17/1978 [for: Mr. Beck] - #476 (Box 469)
- George Meany - CBSTV "Face the Nation" 10/2/1977 - #475 (Box 470)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers: CBSTV; NBCTV; Ch.5 TV -- 8/26/1975 - #477 (Box 471)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers: CBSTV -- 12/15/1978 - #478 (Box 472)
- Amalgamated / Jeff Beck Roundtable - #479 (Box 473)
- June 13 + 14 / SS cont. - #481 (Box 474)
- Terkel - 2/24/1979 - #482 (Box 475)
- Economic Issues in American Democracy: the Role of Unions in the American Economy - #483 (Box 476)
- NBC News - 9/4/1978; NBC Today Show - 9/5/1978 - #484 (Box 477)
- Imports Rally Herald Square - April 13, 1977 - #473 (Box 478)
- George Meany "Face" - CBS; Sen. Williams/Hatch NBC; Labor Report ABC - #474, 1978 (Box 479)
- Imports Rally Herald Square - April 13, 1977 - #473 (Box 480)
- Labor Laws: ABCTV; CBSTV -- May 16th, 1978 - #472 (Box 481)
- Labor Law: Rep. Hatch/Chamber of AFLABC Good Morning America -- 5/30/1978 - #480 (Box 482)
- The Neglected White Worker / Michael Schneider - #353 (Box 483)
- Technology & the Unions / Ralph Helstein - #352 (Box 484)
- The Bleak Outlook - Jobs and Machines / Gerard Piel, Robert Theobald and Ralph Helstein - #351 (Box 485)
- Concentrations of Private Power / Walter Reuther (Box 486)
- 37 R. Labor Looks at Itself / Paul Jacobs and UAW - #349 (Box 487)
- The Sources of Labor Power - #348 (Box 488)
- Early Morning Sessions, National Safety Congress 1975 - #347 (Box 489)
- Early Morning Sessions, National Security Congress 1974 - #346 (Box 490)
- Early Morning Sessions, National Safety Congress 1974 - #345 (Box 491)
- Early Morning Sessions, National Safety Congress 1974 - #344 (Box 492)
- More Youth Than Jobs / Robert J. Havighurst, Vernon Jarrett, et. al. - #354 (Box 493)
- National Health Insurance: Now, Later, Never? - #355 (Box 494)
- How Unions Organize - #356 (Box 495)
- Unions & the Library Profession: Aug. 23, 1973 - #357 (Box 496)
- Open System Re-Design / New Technology in Organization Development - #343 (Box 497)
- OD in a Macrosystem - A Three Year Progress Report / New Technology in Organization Development - #342 (Box 498)
- Improving International Relations an Effectiveness Within Multinational Organizations / New Technology in Organization Development - #341 (Box 499)
- The Client as Theorist: An Approach to Individual and Organization Development / New Technology in Organization Development - #340 (Box 500)
- A Line Management Approach to Organization Development / New Technology in Organization Development - #339 (Box 501)
- Managing Conflict Between Groups / New Technology in Organization Development - #338 (Box 502)
- OD in Large Systems / New Technology in Organization Development - #337 (Box 503)
- A "Mixed Model" Strategy for Changing Medical Centers / New Technology in Organization Development - #336 (Box 504)
- Reducing Job Stress Related to Coronary Heart Disease: A Pilot Organization Development Project / New Technology in Organization Development - #335 (Box 505)
- Training in Autonomy and Initiative / New Technology in Organization Development - #334 (Box 506)
- Motivation, Organization Development and Individual Career Achievement / New Technology in Organization Development #333 (Box 507)
- Some Guidelines for Tomorrow's OD / New Technology in Organization Development - #332 (Box 508)
- The D/D Matrix / New Technology in Organization Development - #331 (Box 509)
- Practice Theories in Organization Development / New Technology in Organization Development - #330 (Box 510)
- Model Building: an OD Technology / New Technology in Organization Development - #329 (Box 511)
- NYLHA Conf. Labor Law Reform: Past & Present - 5/22/1993 (Box 512)
  #395 -- 5 Parts -- was removed from box 11, to place in media cabinet
- NYLHA Conf. Labor Law Reform: Past & Present - 5/22/1993 - #395 (Box 513)
- NYLHA Conf. Labor Law Reform: Past & Present - 5/22/1993 - #395 (Box 514)
- NYLHA Conf. Labor Law Reform: Past & Present - 5/22/1993 - #395 (Box 515)
- NYLHA Conf. Labor Law Reform: Past & Present - 5/22/1993 - #395 (Box 516)
- Summer School for Union Women - 1977 (Box 517)
  #394 - -- was removed from box 11, to place in media cabinet
- Summer School for Union Women 1977 - #394 (Box 518)
- Summer School for Union Women 1977 - #394 (Box 519)
- Old Folks Ain't All the Same (Box 520)
  #397 --- was removed from box 11, to place in media cabinet
- Graduation - North Eastern UCLEA Summer School: U Conn, 7/1976 (Box 521)
  #392 -- -- was removed from box 11, to place in media cabinet
- Keith & Rusty McNeil: Working & Union Songs (1 of 2 tapes) - #382 (Box 522)
- Keith & Rusty McNeil: Working & Union Songs (2 of 2 tapes) - #382 (Box 523)
- Not just bread and butter: Union women on disarmament: #393 (Box 524)
- copy of lyrics and information in Accession file (#213) on front (Box 525)
  - The Labor Theater Presents The Bottom Line (Box 525)
    #213
- Being Ourselves / Barbara Kingsolver - 4/7/1991 (Box 526)
  #423
- Barbara Kingsolver - Being Ourselves: 4/7/1991 (Box 527)
- Video digitized from the collection. (Box 529)
- Audio digitized from the collection. (Box 530)
- Kohler Company: belongs to collection 5583 AV, box 9, 1 (Box 531)